purduefed.com 2015-03-15

# Disclosures | Purdue Federal Credit Union - Dedicated to the communities where Purdue University campuses operate.

## Website Procedures

###### Our Online Privacy Practices

Keeping financial and personal information secure is one of our most important responsibilities. Purdue Federal Credit Union is committed to protecting the information of members and visitors who use our website. We value your trust and handle all personal information with care.

As with information we collect through our other means, we use the information you provide online to respond to your needs, service your accounts, and provide you information about other services.

See our detailed member privacy statement below.

###### Secure Transmissions

To ensure information remains confidential, Purdue Federal Credit Union uses encryption technology such as Secure Socket Layer (SSL) to protect information you enter and submit from our website.

###### Email Security

Email is not a secure method of contact. You should NEVER provide information that is sensitive or confidential through unsecured email. We ask that you take care when contacting us via email and that you do not use email to send sensitive information such as your member number, Social Security number, card number or PIN to us. If you have questions concerning your account that would require providing this type of sensitive information, you should contact the Credit Union by telephone.

###### Cookies

A cookie is small piece of information that a website stores directly on the computer you are using. Cookies can contain a variety of information, from a simple count of how often you visit a website to information that allows customization of a website for your use. Purdue Federal Credit Union uses cookies to gather data about the usage of our website and to ensure that you have access to your account information. Our cookies do not collect or store any personally identifiable information.

###### Linking to Other Sites

Purdue Federal Credit Union’s website contains links to third-party sites. These links are provided for convenience purposes and are not operated by Purdue Federal Credit Union. You will be leaving the Purdue Federal Credit Union’s website upon visiting these links, and a notice will be displayed indicating that.

The information and content provided on these third party websites is neither underwritten nor guaranteed by Purdue Federal Credit Union. Purdue Federal Credit Union is not responsible for the content of the linked website and cannot guarantee the relevance, timeliness or accuracy of the materials provided by other agencies or organizations. Purdue Federal Credit Union does not represent either the third-party or the member if the two enter into a transaction.

Privacy and security policies of non-Purdue Federal websites may differ from those practiced by Purdue Federal Credit Union. We do not control any of these sites and are not responsible for the privacy or security in these sites. While we hope these organizations join us in respecting your privacy, we offer these links only as a convenience to our members. If you choose to link to one of these sites, we strongly suggest that you review their privacy statement, especially prior to entering any non-public information.

###### Member Privacy Statement

Purdue Federal Credit Union (Purdue Federal), your member-owned financial institution, is committed to providing financial products and services to meet your needs and reach your financial goals. We are equally committed to protecting our members’ privacy. You can be confident that your financial privacy is a priority of this credit union. We are required by law to give you this privacy notice to explain how we collect, use and safeguard your personal financial information.

###### Information We Collect and Disclose About You

We collect nonpublic personal information about you from the following sources:

  * Information we receive from you on applications and other forms
  * Information about your transactions with us or others
  * Information we receive from a consumer reporting agency
  * Information obtained when verifying the information you provide on an application or other forms. This may be obtained from your current or past employers, or from other institutions where you conduct financial transactions

We may disclose all the information we collect, as described previously and as permitted by law, to companies that perform marketing services on our behalf or to other financial institutions with whom we have joint marketing agreements. To protect our members’ privacy, we only work with companies that maintain strong confidentiality protections and limit the use of information we provide to other third parties.

In order to conduct the business of the credit union, we may also disclose nonpublic personal information about you under the circumstances as permitted or required by law. These disclosures typically include information to process transactions on your behalf, conduct the operations of our credit union, follow your instructions as you authorize, or protect the security of our financial records.

If you terminate your membership with Purdue Federal Credit Union, we will not share information we have collected about you, except as permitted or required by law.

###### How We Protect Your Information

We restrict access to nonpublic personal information about you to all employees who have a specific business purpose in utilizing your data. Our employees are trained in the importance of maintaining confidentiality and member privacy. We maintain physical, electronic and procedural safeguards that comply with federal regulations and leading industry practices to safeguard your nonpublic personal information.

###### What You Can Do to Help Protect Your Privacy

Purdue Federal Credit Union is committed to protecting the privacy of its members. Members can help by following these simple guidelines:

  * Protect your account numbers, card numbers, PINs (personal identification numbers) and passwords. Never keep your PIN with your debit or credit card, which can provide free access to your accounts if your card is lost or stolen.
  * Use caution when disclosing your account information, Social Security numbers, etc. to other persons. If someone calls you, explains the call is on behalf of the credit union and asks for your account information you should beware. Official credit union staff will have access to your information and will not need to ask for it.
  * Keep your information with us current. It is important that we have current information on how to reach you. If we detect potentially fraudulent or unauthorized activity or use of an account, we will attempt to contact you immediately. If your address or phone numbers change, please let us know.

If you prefer we not disclose nonpublic information about you to nonaffiliated third parties, you may opt-out of these disclosures. To opt-out or if you have questions concerning this notice, please contact us at 765.497.3328 or 800.627.3328 or email us at [mbrservice@purduefed.com](mailto:mbrservice@purduefed.com).

If you have previously notified us about your privacy preferences, it is not necessary to do so again, unless you decide to change your preferences.

  * Member Privacy Statement

View Details

###### Member Disclosures

Find member disclsoures here.

  * Member Services Guide
  * Fee Schedule

  * Online/Mobile/Text Service Agreement

  * Credit Cardholder Benefits

  * Credit Terms/Conditions
  * Choice Rewards Terms/Conditions

View Details

###### Member Business Disclosures

Find business member disclosures and policies here.

  * Business Services Guide
  * Business Fee Schedule
  * Visa Business Credit Card Terms & Conditions

  * Choice Rewards Terms/Conditions
  * Credit Cardholder Benefits

View Details

Print this page
